Preliminary Guide to the Frank Smith, Jr. papers, 1992-1998 MS2182
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Legislative Meeting - Mark Sobo [1/2], 06/01/1998 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Legislative Meeting - Mark Sobo [2/2], 06/01/1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Legislative Meeting - Smith, 06/16/1998 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Committee on Finance & Revenue - Mark-up, 07/22/1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Committee of the Whole - Regular Meeting, 10/21/1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Legislative Meeting - Smith, 09/22/1997 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Legislative Meeting - Smith, 12/04/1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- DC Lottery control board (Box 19, Folder 2)
- DC Lottery reports (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Lottery Board - Keno (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Lottery Board oversight hearing (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Lottery Board - Keno hearing (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Lottery Board - Smith bill (Box 19, Folder 7)
- State lottery info (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Lottery - general (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Lottery Board/Control Board (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Lottery Board - newsletter, news stories (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Lottery - general [1/2] (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Lottery - general [2/2] (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Misc. Legislation (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Public Housing (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Howard University (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Columbia Heights development (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Police boundaries issues (Box 20, Folder 7)
- St. Elizabeth (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Samuel Jackson Plaza (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Proposed legislation (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 11)
- George Washington University (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Adams Morgan (Box 20, Folder 14)
- DC Work Session (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Children's Island (Box 20, Folder 16)
- African American Civil War Memorial (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Garnet-Patterson Gymnasium (Box 20, Folder 18)
- National Children's Island (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Children's Island (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Children's Island (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Children's Island (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Ward One mailing lists (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Miracle celebration for Frank Smith (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Ceremonial resolution (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Pre-Thanksgiving luncheon (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Transmittal of Enrolled Ceremonial Resolution (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Press Releases (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Sample Congratulatory letters (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Labels (Box 21, Folder 11)
- New ANC list (Box 21, Folder 12)
- 5K run 1 mile walk (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Sundry forms (Box 21, Folder 14)
- DC Government Telephone Directory, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Misc. file [1/3], 1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Misc. file [2/3], 1996 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Misc. file [3/3], 1996 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Alcohol Beverage Container Act (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Boards and Commissions Manual (Box 22, Folder 1)
- DC Population reports (Box 22, Folder 2)
- DC Youth reports (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Statistical Index to DC services, 07/1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Economic Development (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Public space (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Parking meters (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Street renamings (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Solid waste regulation (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Vending (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Medicaid contracts (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Daily schedule (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Christmas party (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Teacher & Principal Technology Training (Box 22, Folder 15)
- DC Tax Problems (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Toys for Tots (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Our Children Our Future (Box 22, Folder 18)
- All forms (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Scholarship information (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Letters A-J, 01/1996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Letters A-Z, 30/1996 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Letters A-J, 04/1996 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Lincoln Theater Project info (Box 22, Folder 24)
- NCBA Projects (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Business labels (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Christmas party information, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Business Association lists (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Legislative Drafting manual (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Letters A-J, 08/1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Letters A-J, 07/1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Letters A-J, 01/1996 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Letters A-J, 05/1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Letters A-J, 06/1996 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Letters A-J, 09/1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Letters A-J, 10/1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Letters A-J, 11/1996 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Letters K-T, 01/1996 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Letters K-T, 01/1996 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Letters K-T, 03/1996 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Letters K-T, 04/1996 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Letters K-T, 05/1996 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Letters K-T, 07/1996 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Letters K-T, 08/1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Letters K-T, 09/1996 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Letters K-T, 10/1996 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Letters K-T, 11/1996 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Letters K-T, 06/1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Letters U-Z, 01/1996 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Letters U-Z, 01/1996 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Letters U-Z, 03/1996 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Letters U-Z, 04/1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Letters U-Z, 05/1996 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Letters U-Z, 07/1996 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Letters U-Z, 08/1996 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Letters U-Z, 09/1996 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Letters U-Z, 10/1996 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Letters U-Z, 11/1996 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Letters A-J, 01/1997 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Letters K-T, 01/1997 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Letters U-Z, 01/1997 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Letters, 04/1997 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Letters, 01/1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Letters, 01/1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Letters, 03/1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Letters, 05/199 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Letters, 07/1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Letters, 08/1995 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Letters, 09/1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Letters, 10/1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Letters, 11/1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Letters, 12/1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Letters, 01/1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Letters, 03/1997 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Letters, 05/1997 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Letters, 06/1997 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 15)
- His Excellency Ambassador (Box 24, Folder 16)
- CWM Project (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Mailing labels (Box 24, Folder 18)
- CWM info (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Columbia Heights (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Lincoln Theater (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Ceremonial Resolution (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Low tags (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Memorandum (Box 24, Folder 24)
- NCBA Estates (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Mississippi Foundation Freedom Sumer (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Ward One constituent list (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Caterers (Box 24, Folder 29)
- El Salvador fundraiser (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Topical File - A (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Topical File - B (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Topical File - C (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Topical File - D (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Topical File - E (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Topical File - F (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Topical File - G (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Topical File - H (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Topical File - I (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Topical File - J (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Topical File - K (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Topical File - L (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Topical File - M (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Topical File - N (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Topical File - O (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Topical File - P (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Topical File - Q (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Topical File - S (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Topical File - T (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Topical File - U (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Topical File - V (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Topical File - W (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Topical File - Z (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Lucy Blackburn (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Homestead (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Old Schedules (Box 25, Folder 26)
- DC Employers Directory, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Comp Plan for National Capital District Elements (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Capital improvement reports (Box 26, Folder 3)
- DC Budget & Financial Plan, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Historic sites (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Environmental assessment, 06/1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Religious Freedom report, 05/1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- DC Statistical indeces, 12/1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Civil War Memorial (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Law Regarding Ethics (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Finance & Revenue info (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Requisition for services, supplies (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Councilmember statements (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Media list (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Columbia Heights (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Information systems (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Housing (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Ward One information (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Constituent complaints (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Smith bio (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Constituent complaint forms (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Compensatory overtime sheets (Box 27, Folder 1)
- EOFULA/Latino list (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Dept of Public Works (Box 27, Folder 3)
- ANC list and ifno (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Blank forms (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Work in progress (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Proposed legislation (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Comp Plan [1/2] (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Comp Plan [2/2] (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Civil War Memorial - programs, press, info (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Civil War Memorial - pictures (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Civil War Memorial - displays (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Civil War Memorial - displays (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Ward One banner (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Civil War Memorial memorabilia, resolution (Box 28, Folder 1)